eucerinus.com 2017-06-25

# Privacy Policy | Eucerin

### Privacy Policy

1\. Policy scope and purpose, changes to the policy

Beiersdorf, Inc. (“Beiersdorf”) respects the privacy of its users and recognizes the importance of providing a secure environment for them.  We know that you care how information about you is used and shared.  This privacy policy describes how we collect, store, and use the information you provide to us.  You should carefully review this privacy policy before using this website or services provided through this website.  This privacy policy applies only to information collected through this website and not to any information collected from us or through us offline.  Please note that, when you link to other websites from this website, this privacy policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities on, those other sites.  Please check those websites for their own privacy policies.

You should carefully review this privacy policy before using this website.  By so using this website or taking advantage of any service accessed through this website, you signify your assent to this privacy policy.  If you do not agree to this privacy policy, please do not use this website or our services accessed through it.  This privacy policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes.  Your continued use of this website will signify your acceptance of those changes.

2\. What personal information is collected?

We collect information from you when you register on this website, join Club Blue, respond to a survey or to a communication such as an email, or use other services on this website.  We store that information ourselves or by the use of third parties under contract with us.  Those other services may include, for example, the creation of a profile page, participation in forums or the provision of facilities to permit you to post media content such as images and text.

Some of the information that we collect from you is defined as personally identifiable information about an individual, as more particularly described under applicable privacy laws (“Personal Information”).  Personal Information may include, without limitation: your name, age, mailing address, email address, telephone number, credit card information and related financial information, information concerning your interests, occupation, product uses and preferences, and other demographic information that could help identify you.  If you have set up an account that is password protected in order to play online games, to purchase goods or for any other purpose for which a password is needed, that password is also part of your Personal Information.  It may be possible to use portions of this website without providing any Personal Information, but it may be necessary to provide Personal Information to utilize all features of this website.

3\. What other types of information may we collect?

For some activities, your web browser or client software may transmit certain geographic information or information regarding your computer to Beiersdorf.  Beiersdorf may use that information to generate aggregate statistics about our user community and may provide that information to advertisers and other parties with whom we have a business relationship.  In addition, Beiersdorf may use any such information for security, system integrity (the prevention of hacking, cheating and other improper or unlawful activities), or enforcement purposes.

Beiersdorf may also identify and track your Internet protocol (“IP”) address.  An IP address is the unique number assigned to your server or internet service provider (“ISP”).   Beiersdorf may track those IP addresses for system administration purposes, to report aggregate information, site tracking, security purposes, or to prevent our data and servers from being damaged.

When you visit this website, we may, at our option, automatically collect and store the following types of non-personally identifiable information received from you: (i) information from server logs found on your browser; (ii) click-through statistics; (iii) your country; (iv) the type of web browser you are using to access this website; (v) the type of operating system you are using; (vi) the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; (vii) the date and time you access this website and the duration of your visit; and (viii) the Internet address of the site from which you linked directly to this website.  Automatically collected information of that kind typically provides us with a greater understanding regarding the use of this website, including which pages are the most popular with our visitors.  That information also allows us to determine if this website is working properly and to make changes to the website that allows users to have better experiences on the website.  We collect that information and track it for statistical purposes; we do not use it to identify or to market to a particular user.

This website is not intended for children.  We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personal Information about visitors under 13 years of age. For more information please see Section 11, What About Children, below.

4\. How secure is your Personal Information?

Beiersdorf has taken reasonable steps to provide that all Personal Information collected by us through this website will remain secure.  For example, for credit card information that is transmitted to us, we use industry-standard, SSL (secure sockets layer) encryption.  In addition, we take reasonable steps to require that third parties to whom we transfer any data will provide sufficient protection of Personal Information received from us.

You can help us to protect your Personal Information by: (i) using a secure web browser; (ii) not sharing any password or log-in data with others; and (iii) changing your password frequently.

5\. How do we use your Personal Information?

The Personal Information you provide to Beiersdorf will allow us to do the following: (i) fulfill your orders for goods and services; (ii) alert you of new products or services, features, updates and enhancements; (iii) handle your customer service or technical support questions or issues; (iv) personalize your experience while using our services; (v) deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested; and (vi) notify you of upgrade opportunities, contests, promotions, or special events and offers.  We may enhance or merge the Personal Information collected at a Beiersdorf website with data provided to us by others.

We do not sell, rent, license, trade or exchange Personal Information with or to any third parties, except as otherwise provided in this privacy policy.

We may share your Personal Information among our affiliates worldwide.  They may use your Personal Information to offer products and services to you consistent with the purposes identified in this privacy policy.  We may use your Personal Information for internal marketing, profiling or demographic purposes, so we can adapt our products and services, the better to suit your anticipated needs.

6\. What are cookies and how do we use them?

A cookie is a small bit of computer code that we send to your computer and is stored on your hard drive.  It allows a website to transfer bits of information to your computer for record-keeping purposes.  A cookie stored in your computer can be used to “remember” specific data items such as your password or operational information, such as the fact that you have already subscribed to the full version of a particular online game.  That allows us to speed up your future activities, saving the time you would normally spend entering information such as your password or subscription information.  In addition, Beiersdorf may use cookies to retrieve user information for promotional, marketing, or security purposes.

7\. Does Beiersdorf disclose personal Information it collects to outside parties?

Beiersdorf may need to disclose items of your Personal Information to third-party vendors to fulfill product orders or prizes, to process mailings, or to process, analyze, or store data on Beiersdorf’s behalf.  Those third parties are not authorized by Beiersdorf to use or disclose your Personal Information for any purpose other than for use in connection with the provision of services designated by us or the delivery and processing of orders for goods.  We will take reasonable measures to have those third parties maintain the confidentiality, security, and integrity of the Personal Information they obtain from us.

We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information as required or permitted by law.  For example, we may disclose it to respond to a subpoena, court order or other legal process, or in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing Personal Information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against you if we reasonably believe that you may be violating your agreements with us (including, without limitation, any applicable terms of use), or may be causing injury to, or interference with, Beiersdorf, any other user of this website or any service, the general public or other third parties. You may be asked whether you wish to receive information from third parties; upon your consent, Beiersdorf or those third parties may use your Personal Information to contact you. However, please be aware that Beiersdorf cannot control the activities of third parties to whom we provide data; we therefore cannot guarantee that they will adhere to similar privacy and security procedures as Beiersdorf.

8\. The transfer of Personal Information.

The Personal Information you provide to Beiersdorf may be transferred as an asset in connection a merger or sale involving all or part of Beiersdorf or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or other change of control. As part of its business operations, Beiersdorf may transfer Personal Information to recipients in countries that do not provide the same level of legal data protection as the country from which you access our website or services.  By using Beiersdorf’s website or services, you consent to the transfer of Personal Information and to the processing by Beiersdorf of that Personal Information.

9\. Who is collecting your information?

When you are asked for information while on this website, you are sharing that information with Beiersdorf, its parent, and its various affiliates and sister companies, unless specifically stated otherwise.  As a result of that sharing, you may receive communications from any of those Beiersdorf affiliates.  In addition, some services offered by Beiersdorf through this website are provided in conjunction with third parties with which Beiersdorf has a business relationship.  If your Personal Information is being collected by a company other than Beiersdorf, you will be so notified at the time that the process for the collection of that Personal Information is initiated.  If you do not want to have your Personal Information so shared, please do not elect to use the service or facility for which that Personal Information is collected.

10\. How can you manage your personal information?

At the time you provide personal information, Beiersdorf will give you the option of declining any future offers or information about new products, promotions, or services.  In addition, many of the messages that Beiersdorf may send you, such as electronic newsletters, have procedures within them to cancel the receipt of similar information in the future or later editions.  You may also be given the opportunity to “opt out” of certain features or functions.

11\. What about Children?

This website is designed by Beiersdorf and intended to be considered as a general audience website and is not intended for use by children.  Beiersdorf does not intend to collect Personal Information from individual under the age of thirteen.  If you are the parent or guardian of a child under thirteen who has provided Personal Information to us, please contact us by clicking here: Contact Us.  You can also contact us by e-mailing us at consumerrelations@bdfusa.com.  Please note for your reference the potential effects of deletion, at Section 13.

12\. How do you correct or delete your Personal Information or file a complaint?

If, for any reason, you are concerned about the way we are using your Personal Information, or you would like to correct or request that we delete any item of Personal Information, please contact us by clicking here: Contact Us .  You can also contact us by e-mailing us at consumerrelations@bdfusa.com.

13\. Deletion of Personal Information and the use of Beiersdorf online games.

You are not required to provide us with any Personal Information we request, but the failure to provide certain items of Personal Information may prevent you from using some website functions.  You may, at any time, delete any of your Personal Information earlier provided to us.  However, please note that the deletion of certain items of your Personal Information may prevent the provision to you of certain services.

14\. Contact Us.

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

Consumer Relations  
Beiersdorf Inc   
45 Danbury Rd   
Wilton, CT 06897   
Tel: 1-800-227-4703  
Email: consumerrelations@bdfusa.com  

15\. California Privacy Rights.

Under California law, if you are a California resident, you have the right to request that we do not share your Personal information with third parties for use in direct marketing by them to you.  To make such a request, please write us at:

Consumer Relations   
Beiersdorf Inc   
45 Danbury Rd   
Wilton, CT 06897

This privacy policy was last updated January 2012
